I realized early that I needed my kids to heal because they're like really like the best parts
of the both of us put together. Like that's one thing we acknowledged when he was here and I can
see it. And like I said, my son, he just like embodies him like the serious side, the business
side, the brain side. That's dog. My daughter embodies the silly side. She's so silly. And artsy.
And artsy. Like they went to school. My son went to school. I'm like, I'm so proud of my mom. Have
you heard a black man deserve to grow old? She's doing that because of my dad and my uncle. She
been on ABC. You watch the news? Like, so they're so proud. And I just invite them in. Like
they're so happy when I invite them into the space of like creating. I'm like, y'all, I
want y'all to learn. I can't teach y'all how to be a businessman like y'all daddy. Cause
he was cold with it. I ain't, I ain't learning from him. I watched him, but he ain't work
with me as a mentor, like mentee type of thing. Look, you can do all the learning you want
to. If you want to create designs, if you want to, my daughter, like I want to be a
fashion designer. Can I be the youngest? I'm like, you can explore with this.
Yeah.
I love you.
Yeah, you're crazy.
All right.
Bye.